





Summary

Last Active: 22-Jan-21

Jump to Section

AMulti-skilled IT Professional with good all-round supervisory and technical expertise. Very capable with a proven ability to ensure the smooth running of ICT (information and communication technologies) systems and to provide IT services that will improve the efficiency and performance of a company. Extensive practical knowledge of complex system builds hardware and software testing, IT Infrastructure and technical support.

Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Work Experience

Bose Corporation India Pvt. Ltd. as IT Business Process Analyst Jul 2013 to Till Date

Support and develop departmental processes, such as change management, incident management or problem management Develop consistent operational reporting against standards and establish Service Level Agreement (SLA).

Effectively manage time, prioritize, assign, and manage daily workloads

Administer efficient working of IT Operations team and achieve all objectives

Analyze design feasibility of all IT infrastructure process and

Develop system to adapt to changing technologies.

KEYPROJECTS DELIVERED

SharePoint Project (Acc Recon s/w) Implementation Year - 2018

Scope: Asia Pacific

Resource: SharePoint Online, Microsoft Azure Languages Used: HTML, CSS, jQuery, Ajax

Engagement: Business stake holders in Asia Pacific and Vendor

GST Implementation in Point of Sales

Year - 2017

Scope: Pan India retail outlets

Target Systems: POS(ETP), SAP and Integration Engagement: India Business stake holders and Vendors

VAT Implementation in Point of Sales in Dubai

Year - 2017

Scope: Pan Dubai retail outlets

Tarnet Sixtems: POS/FTP), SAP and Integration

Important

· Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

Engagement: India Business stake holders and Vendors

Biometric attendance management system

Year - 2015

Scope: All India Bose locations

Development: Vendor s/w and centralized Integration Engagement: India Business stake holders and Vendor

Religare Wellness Limited as Assistant Manager IT

Aug 2008 to Jul 2013

Managing and Monitoring Database Servers and keeping it in optimal

condition

Provide PC and network support by overseeing the administration of

the Local Area Network (LAN) for all assigned facilities

Evaluate all plans and perform tests on disaster recovery process.

Listening to problems and providing Solutions in Applications of Frontend Stores and Warehouses.

Maintaining the Legacy applications and providing on demand data.

Managing and Monitoring Exchange Server and Active Directory.

KEYPROJECTS DELIVERED

POS (Vinculum) Implementation

Year - 2009

Scope: Pan India Retail outlets

Challenges: Migrate data from old POS to new POS, Establish

Integration with SAP

Engagement: India Business stake holders and Vendor

Asiatic Electrical & Switchgear Private Limited as System Administrator

Nov 2005 to Jul 2008

Job Profile

Maintaining in house Developed Applications and giving support to

end users.

Report preparation from MS SQL server.

Troubleshooting ERP Software and coordinating with Vendor in

Application Issues.

Managing and Monitoring Exchange Server and AD server and creating

user mailbox account with applied policies

Hardware Management and procurement for entire IT systems. Technical Support to users.

KEYPROJECTS DELIVERED

AD and Exchange Server Implementation

Year - 2007

Scope: Within the company premise
Servers: Windows Server 2003 & Exchange Server 2003 ERP-Reckonner (Manufacturing Module) Implementation

Year - 2006

Scope: Within the company premise

Engagement: Business stake holders and Vendor

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Sc (Maths) from North Orissa University (NOU) in 2000

PG: MBA/PGDM (Information Technology) from SVSU University in 2019

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
MS SQL, MySQL			
Oracle			
TABLEAU			
UI PATH			
JavaScript			
Sharepoint, office 365			
SHAREPOINT DESIGNER			
InfoPath & PowerApps			
AD, Exchange, DNS, DHCP			
VLAN, VPN			
BMC ITSM, Cherwell			

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.